♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
=The One=
=Episode 8=
(Sun Ye)
Hello?
I'll take the fight.
See you in a bit.
There you are.
Darn.
Wait, wait, wait!
Huh?
Y-you...
Did you just crawl out of
some woman's bed?
Can you still fight?
Just need to warm up.
Hey.
Bao.
He's my student.
Hasn't fought in five years.
He's here to shake off the rust
and make some money.
Give it your best, kid.
Come on.
Go get changed first.
(That's a good shot.)
(Underground Fight Club)
Make some room, everyone.
Thanks, everyone.
(Just like five years ago.)
(Stay loose.)
You've got this!
(Did you get that?)
(Nice one!)
(Don't hurt him too badly.)
Round one.
Ready.
Fight!
(Still showing off?)
(One punch! Send him home!)
(Come on!)
(What are your plans?)
(School?)
(Or do you want to learn a trade?)
(Before I got out,)
(I had a lot of things in mind.)
(Come on!)
- One.
- (Come on!)
Two.
Three.
(Come on!)
Winner!
Yeah!
(Whoa!)
(Don't judge a book by its cover!)
(He's got skills!)
(Not bad!)
(Awesome!)
(Amazing! Amazing!)
(That was so cool!)
(Go! Go!)
(He's amazing!)
(Nice! Nice!)
Why so cocky?
Hey!
(Now this is a real match.)
(Dodge!)
Hey, time!
(He's done, right?)
Time!
(Keep fighting!)
- Are you trying to get yourself killed?
- (Get up!)
Foul. That's one warning.
If you can't beat him, just give up!
You'll get yourself killed!
One.
Why are you getting back up?
Two.
You can't beat him.
Three.
Just give up!
Four.
I won't quit.
Focus on his left side and left leg.
You good?
Let's go again.
(Come on!)
(Push forward! Get him!)
(Hit harder!)
Winner!
Yeah!
(Amazing!)
(That's amazing!)
You must be exhausted.
Have some water.
How come you're here?
Stop it.
Watch out!
Not mad anymore?
Since when was I mad?
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
It hurts.
Maybe you could kiss it better?
I heard saliva
helps with swelling.
You sure know how to flirt.
So you were playing innocent before?
No.
I-I'm just really happy.
If it weren't for you, I...
I wouldn't have won.
Enough with the flattery.
Why are you fighting underground?
Is this how you plan to make a living?
Yes.
Sun and I want to open a boxing gym.
I started boxing when I was ten.
Sun was my coach.
Before I went in,
I won a junior championship.
I heard you got into trouble
protecting your mom.
What happened?
Su Yan.
You really don't remember any of it?
Remember what?
Nothing.
Do you want
to grab something to eat?
Are you hungry?
Well, well.
Now that's a feisty one.
Come have some fun with us,
and we'll let your boy toy go.
(Su Yan.)
(Tell me.)
(What would make you feel better?)
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪
♪Memories pile up, moment by moment♪
♪One careless word brings my walls down♪
♪I escape the past, then fall back in♪
♪Longing twists into a hopeless knot♪
♪Pulled by the past
till my world fades out♪
♪I hum this song alone♪
♪Counting every fleeting moment♪
♪Every corner still reminds me of you♪
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪